<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Legal on Kriti/ Directory</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/legal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Legal on Kriti/ Directory</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/legal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Kriti Directory&lt;/strong&gt;, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by &lt;strong&gt;Kriti Directory&lt;/strong&gt; and how we use it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:vinay.gaykar@proton.me&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collected on &lt;a href=&#34;https://kriti.directory&#34;&gt;https://kriti.directory&lt;/a&gt;. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refund Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/legal/refund-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/legal/refund-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you for shopping at &lt;strong&gt;Kriti Directory&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following terms are applicable for any products that you have purchased from us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;eligibility-for-refunds&#34;&gt;Eligibility for Refunds&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We offer refunds under the following circumstances:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If the service is not delivered as promised due to an error on our end.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If a technical issue caused by our platform prevents you from accessing the features you paid for, and the issue cannot be resolved within a reasonable timeframe.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you cancel your subscription within the refund period outlined below.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;refund-period&#34;&gt;Refund Period&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refund requests must be made within &lt;strong&gt;30&lt;/strong&gt; days of the payment date. Requests made after this period will not be eligible for a refund.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms Of Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/legal/terms-of-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/legal/terms-of-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using Our Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgment&#34;&gt;Acknowledgment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These are the Terms and Conditions governing the use of this Service and the agreement that operates between you and the Company. These Terms and Conditions set out the rights and obligations of all users regarding the use of the Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions apply to all visitors, users, and others who access or use the Service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
